[{"answer": "No, I'm not angry.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Tell me why?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you know, the old days, we had generals like Patton and Robert E. Lee and we had some great ones, General Douglas MacArthur, Grant.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "And indeed with the wider issue of America's place on the world stage and in the Middle East in particular?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, we allow them but we don't encourage it.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Would you ever allow such a thing in your pageants Donald Trump?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, I mean first of all.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What do you think of where we are with Syria?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I mean, I think that while we have peace process in place that may lead to the removal of chemical weapons, then I don't think we should strike.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Military action?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "That would be a real win for international security if those chemical weapons were removed.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "If it ends up with the chemical weapons being removed and being seemed to be removed from Assad but he stays in power, is that still a victory at any time?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "You know, I'm not a fan of arbitrary rules that target certain classes of people, except criminals.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Are you a fan of that?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Look on first blush it does sound totally preposterous and ridiculous.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Van Jones am I loosing the plot?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "No I wouldn't but I'll tell you what Piers...", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "I ask you both again, would you be happy for the veteran in the scenario that Van Jones just pictured for me to be a New York cab driver if they so wanted?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Watch tonight when Ricky Gervais enters my lair.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "The chair in the lair.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "That's -- that's worrying isn't it?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Well it's scary because there is a man in a pink tie.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "What does it conjures up to you?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I could only hope.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Did you ever think in your early chubby days, ever have that kind of headline in this six months?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "I like him, he's enjoying his food.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Yeah, no, not at all.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Would you see him as a figure of fun?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Well I can run, I can run and it strapped up but I can't be wasting money so I ran, I still ran everyday.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Now how can you work out, given that I couldn't shake your right hand because of this terrible tendonitis you've got?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I'm on pain killers so...", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "You're in agony right?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Don't know.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "So, how many months have you have this?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "A frozen shoulder.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Only two things really, really make my blood boil I suppose.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "What are the, you said the things you like, what are the things that really annoy you?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Yeah I had that ones in the tabloid, they were saying about Rick Gervais should be banned from television, his life I think disgust me, talks about just all of the holocaust right and it's then, my friends went to see him in Brighton, well no that's it...", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "But how can you possibly review it?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Well wanted Derek.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "But what was the purpose of this creation?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "You can't.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Underneath I'm like a duck.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Subliminal twerking?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Well they're constitutional right?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Would be damage if -- and they gave an example of, you know, if they were fully sighted and used the gun just because they lost their sight, why should they lives to constitutional right to continue having a gun?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "So, the constitution covers everyone, does it?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "I would not be allowed to carry gun here in New York, but I could carry one in, you know, Dallas or I can carry one anywhere.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "But tell me, you are not allowed to carry a gun?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "That is the big one.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Pick up?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Three times, yeah.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "You've done it three times, right?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I think -- worry about the TV audience, do it for them.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "What is the -- what is the technique to handling that notoriously difficult crowd?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "The one that sprang to mind was the first Golden Globes.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What would you choose?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "I don't know, 'cause I shouldn't have won it.", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "(inaudible)", "docId": "130913pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "What's the answer?", "qSentId": 529}]